http://www.eaglesfield.com/acatalog/privacy-policy.html

Football TrophiesResin Football TrophiesCrystal Football TrophiesSwatkins Football TrophiesJust Rewards Football TrophiesTrendsetting Football TrophiesFootball MedalsSalversFootball MetalwareWooden Football HolderGolf AwardsResin Golf AwardsCrystal / Glass Golf TrophiesSwatkins Golf TrophiesJust Rewards Golf TrophiesTrendsetting Golf TrophiesGolf MedalsSalversGolf
MetalwareWooden Golf Ball HolderRugby AwardsResin Rugby AwardsCrystal / Glass Rugby TrophiesRugby MedalsSalversWooden Rugby Ball HolderCricket AwardsResin Cricket AwardsGlass / Crystal Cricket AwardsJust Rewards Cricket AwardsTrendsetting Cricket AwardsCricket MedalsBoxing AwardsDarts AwardsOther Sports AwardsAthleticsBasketball / NetballBowlsEquestrianMotor SportSnooker / PoolSwimmingTable TennisTennisBlank medals, boxes & ribbonsCorporate AwardsJust Rewards GlasswarePlaques / SalversCrystal PlaquesMemorial PlaquesSublimation PlaquesSalvers
InformationHomePrivacy PolicyTrophy EngravingHow To Find Us Delivery ChargesTestimonials    follow us on Facebook follow us on Twitter  Cookies and PrivacyEaglesfield TrophiesPrivacy PolicyEaglesfield Trophies is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy explains our data processing practices and your options regarding the ways in which your personal data is used. If you have any requests concerning your personal information or any queries with regard to our processing please contact us at sales@eaglesfield.comCookies"Cookies" are small pieces of information sent by a web server to a web browser, which enables the server to collect information from the browser. You can find out more about the way cookies work on www.cookiecentral.com. Eaglesfield Trophies has minimised its use of such mechanisms and only use them to enable smooth processing between pages during the purchase of a product and for traffic monitoring using Google Analytics.You do not need to allow your browser to accept cookies in order to browse much of our web site or to access many of our services.Most browsers allow you to turn off the cookie function. If you want to know how to do this please look at the help menu on your browser.Information collectedEaglesfield Trophies collects the details provided by you on making an enquiry either online or by telephone/fax. We also monitor traffic patterns and site use which enables us to improve the service we provide. Use of your information and your preferencesWe will use your information to provide and personalise our service. We will also use your contact details to communicate with you. We may use your information to send you offers from time to time. We may contact you by post, email, telephone or fax for these purposes.Please note that there may be instances where it may be necessary for us to communicate with you, in any event, for administrative or operational reasons relating to our service. Disclosures of your informationWe will never pass your personal data to anyone else, except for any successors in title to our business and suppliers that process data on our behalf.Other web sitesOur web site may contain links to other web sites which are outside our control and are not covered by this Privacy Policy. If you access other sites using the links provided, the operators of these sites may collect information from you which will be used by them in accordance with their privacy policy, which may differ from ours.     Terms and Conditions; Privacy Policy; Site Map; How to find UsEaglesfield: 18 Vyse Street; Hockley; Birmingham;
B18 6LE; United Kingdom© 2011 - 2020 Eaglesfield
